valetmag.com 2015-06-23

# Valet. > About > Legal > Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Updated on November 23, 2010  |  Created on June 1, 2008

## Scope of this Online Privacy Statement

This Online Privacy Statement describes how Valet Media LLC uses, shares and protects the personal information we collect through valetmag.com ("valetmag.com" or "this site"). "Personal information" is information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information. Personal information may include, for example, your name, address, and email address. This Online Privacy Statement is part of and incorporated into the valetmag.com [Terms & Conditions](http://www.valetmag.com/about/terms_conditions.php).

## Your Consent to This Online Privacy Statement

By browsing or using valetmag.com, you are agreeing to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Online Privacy Statement. If you do not consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Online Privacy Statement, you should not use this site.

## Questions Concerning Our Online Privacy Practices

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Online Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please e-mail [legal](mailto:legal@valetmag.com).

## Privacy Notices

This Online Privacy Statement may be supplemented or amended from time to time by "privacy notices" posted on this site.

## This Online Privacy Statement May Change

We reserve the right to update or modify this Online Privacy Statement, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on this site. These changes will only apply to personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Online Privacy Statement on this site. Your use of this site following any such change constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you through valetmag.com after the revised Online Privacy Statement is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Online Privacy Statement.

To alert you to changes to this Online Privacy Statement, we will provide a notice at the top of this Online Privacy Statement for at least 30 days after the new effective date of such changes and highlight the changes so that you can locate them easily.

You may access the current version of this Online Privacy Statement at any time by clicking on the link marked "Privacy Policy" at the bottom of each page of this site.

## What Personal Information Do We Collect on valetmag.com?

**Information You Give Us**  
We collect the personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide when you use valetmag.com, for example, the information you provide when you participate in a contest or questionnaire, submit product reviews, sign up for our e-mail newsletters, or communicate with customer service. Depending on how you use this site, you may supply us with information such as your name, address, phone number, email address.

**Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser**  
We collect information that is sent to us by your Web browser, such as your IP address, the address of the Web page you were visiting when you accessed valetmag.com, the date and time of your visit, and information about your computer's operating system. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. The information provided by your browser does not identify you personally. We use this non-personal information primarily to create statistics that help us improve this site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors.

**Information We Collect Using Cookies and Other Web Technologies**  
We use "cookies" and other Web technologies to collect information and support certain features of this site. For example, we use these technologies to collect information about the ways visitors use our site - which pages they visit, which links they use, and how long they stay on each page. Generally, the information we collect using these Web technologies does not identify you personally, however, it may be linked to information that does identify you personally, such as the information you provide when you make a purchase or register to use a special feature of our site. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you may set your browser to reject cookies or to alert you when a cookie is placed on your computer. You may also delete our cookies as soon as you leave valetmag.com. Although you are not required to accept our cookies when you visit valetmag.com, if you set your browser to reject cookies, you will not be able to use all of the features and functionality of this site.

## Use of Cookies and Similar Technologies by Our Advertising Agents

Valetmag.com uses third-party advertising companies to place online advertisements on our behalf at websites other than valetmag.com. These advertising companies may use cookies and Web beacons (also known as "pixel tags") to target and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements. For example, our advertising companies may place Web beacons on their clients' Web sites. When you visit these Web sites, the Web beacon "tags" your computer with a "cookie" that collects and stores information about your visit to their client's Web site. This information does not identify you personally. Our advertising companies use the information they collect about your use of their clients' Web sites to customize the advertisements you see when you visit their clients' Web sites. Our advertising companies' use of cookies and Web beacons is covered by their privacy policies, not by this Online Privacy Policy. If you'd like to opt-out of behavioral advertising from our participating third-party advertising companies, please [complete this form](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## How Do We Use Your Personal Information?

We may use the personal information we collect through valetmag.com

  * to provide you with the information, products and services you request or purchase;
  * for security, credit or fraud prevention purposes;
  * to provide you with effective customer service;
  * to display personalized advertising when you visit this site;
  * to contact you with special offers and other information we believe will be of interest to you;
  * to contact you with information and notices related to your use of this site;
  * to invite you to participate in surveys and provide feedback to us;
  * to better understand the your needs and interests;
  * to improve the content, functionality and usability of this site;
  * to improve our products and services;
  * to improve our marketing and promotional efforts; and
  * for any other purpose we identify in a specific privacy notice.

## With Whom Do We Share the Personal Information We Collect Through Valetmag.com?

We may share the personal information we collect through this site as described below and in any applicable privacy notices.

**Our Corporate Affiliates**  
We may share your personal information with our subsidiaries and parent and sister corporations (our "corporate affiliates"), including Valet Media LLC, who may use this information to contact you with information and offers they believe will be of interest to you. The corporate affiliates' use of your personal information shall be subject to this Online Privacy Statement.

**Our Service Providers**  
We may share your personal information with companies that perform services on our behalf. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide services on our behalf.

**Other Business Partners and Selected Vendors**  
We work closely with certain business partners and carefully selected vendors to provide you with access to their product offerings. We may share personally identifiable information about you with these business partners or selected vendors, and they may use this information to offer you products and/or services that they believe will be of interest to you.

**Business Transfers**  
Information submitted to valetmag.com is an asset of Valet Media LLC and will become part of our normal business records. Your personal information may be transferred to another company (either a corporate affiliate or an unrelated third party) that has acquired substantially all the assets of Valet Media LLC, one of our corporate affiliates, or one of our operating divisions, for example, as the result of a sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or liquidation. Valetmag.com shall provide notice of such transfer by posting an update to the top of this Online Privacy Policy.

**Government and Legal Disclosures**  
We may disclose the personal information we collect through valetmag.com when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce the Terms of Use or other agreements that govern your use of this site; to protect the rights, property or safety of Valet Media LLC, our users or others; or to protect your vital interests.

## What Choices Do You Have?

Valetmag.com respects your right to make choices about the ways we collect, use and disclose your personal information. You may browse valetmag.com without providing any information that identifies you personally and may choose not to provide the information we request, although this may mean that you can not take advantage of other valetmag.com features. We may periodically send you information and product promotions via e-mail. You may "opt-out" of receiving our promotional e-mails at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of the particular newsletter or e-mail.

## Security

Valet Media LLC has industry standard measures in place to protect the security of the personal information we collect through valetmag.com. It is important that you understand, however, that no Web site or database is completely secure or "hacker proof." You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse, for example, by protecting your passwords.

## Links to Other Web Sites

Valetmag.com contains links to other Web sites operated by Valet Media LLC and its corporate affiliates and service partners. It also contains links to Web sites that are owned and operated by unrelated third parties. This Online Privacy Policy applies only to personal information collected through valetmag.com. It does not apply to personal information collected on any other Web site operated by Valet Media LLC or its corporate affiliates, nor to any Web site operated by any third party. These Web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. We recommend you review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information about yourself.

## Children and Minors

Valetmag.com is not directed at nor targeted to children. We do not use this site to knowingly solicit personal information from or market to children. If you are under 13 years of age, you should not submit any personal information to us.
